Timothy Wangwe

Nairobi, Kenya



linkedin.com/in/timothy-wangwe



wangwetymothy@gmail.com



0706659609

Summary

Timothy has always had a dream of being Iron Man since childhood. A decade later, he is (currently) pursuing a B.S. in Information Technology. He has a passion for and specialises in Data Science and Machine Learning. He is also quite experienced in Software Development and Web Development Technologies.

He is a leader who believes in transformational leadership; Tim is well experienced in working with young people, teams and other leaders. He can communicate flawlessly in writing and is well equipped with public speaking skills and public relations.

In University, I started a club that progressively mobilises students for humanitarian and environmental causes within and around the institution's vicinity. I could only achieve as much by inspiring members of the club to stand for change and growth.

Experience

...

Campus Ambassador

Moringa School

Apr 2020 - Present (5 months +)

My main responsibility is to generate new leads among the campus population by using the following tactics:

- Identify and actively introduce Moringa School to campus groups/leaders.
- Developing creative ideas to assist in campus outreach efforts
- Identifying the types of events most likely to engage students' imaginations and interests, and strategies to encourage attendance.

且 M

Mathematics - Physics Tutor

Kibunde High School

Jan 2019 - Apr 2019 (4 months)

My responsibilities were anchored in the following areas:

- Teach Physics to Forms 1 and 2
- Teach Mathematics to Forms 1 and 3
- Lead the Revision Programme for the Candidate Class

Impact

- Mentored 3 candidates to qualify for university

Education



Zetech University

Bachelor's degree, Information Technology 2019 - 2022

Licenses & Certifications

- Cloud Intro IBM
- Data Science & Analytics Intro IBM
- Artificial Intelligence Intro IBM
- Python for Data Science Essential Training Part 1 LinkedIn
- in Python for Data Science Essential Training Part 2 LinkedIn
- Building RESTful Web APIs with Django LinkedIn
- in Django: Forms LinkedIn
- Web Graphics and CSS Pseudo-Elements LinkedIn
- Building a Personal Portfolio with Django LinkedIn
- Essential Math for Machine Learning LinkedIn
- in Body Language for Leaders LinkedIn

Honors & Awards

International President's Award for Distinguished Leo Presidents(2019-2020) - Lions Club International

Nov 2019

A multiple district council of governors or single district (that is not part of a multiple districts) may nominate one high achieving Leo each year for this medallion and certificate award.

Skills

Machine Learning Algorithms • Data Analysis • Django • Web Development • Analytics • Analytical Skills • Programming • Python (Programming Language) • Leadership • Team Management